Guide to the Stanford University, Vice President for Business Affairs, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Medical Center - Governor’s Lane Complex - Bid Packages, Invitations and Summaries, 734, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 38)
- Medical Center - Governor’s Lane Complex - Disbursements, 734, 1973-1977 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Medical Center - Governor’s Lane Complex - Legal, 734, 1972-1976 (Box 106, Folder 2)
- Medical Center - Hospital Expansion, Phase I Site Clearance - Bulletins, Supplements, 592A, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 16)
- Medical Center - Hospital Expansion, Phase I Site Clearance - Affirmative Action Program, 592A, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 19)
- Medical Center - Hospital Expansion, Phase I Site Clearance - Budget, 592A, 1973-1977 (Box 105, Folder 14)
- Medical Center - Hospital Expansion, Phase I Site Clearance - Contract Changes, 592A, 1973-1974 (Box 105, Folder 15)
- Medical Center - Hospital Expansion, Phase I Site Clearance - Disbursements, 592A, 1973-1977 (Box 105, Folder 13)
- Medical Center - Hospital Expansion, Phase I Site Clearance - Exhibits, 592A, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 21)
- Medical Center - Hospital Expansion, Phase I Site Clearance - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, 592A, 1973-1974 (Box 105, Folder 18)
- Medical Center - Hospital Expansion, Phase I Site Clearance - General Correspondence, 592A, 1972-1977 (Box 105, Folder 17)
- Medical Center - Hospital Expansion, Phase I Site Clearance - Legal, 592A, 1973-1974 (Box 105, Folder 20)
- Medical Center - Hospital Expansion, Phase I Site Clearance - Testing Laboratory, (empty) (Box 105, Folder 22)
- Medical Center - Neurology Shell Completion, 1971-1974 (Box 115, Folder 30)
- Medical Center - NIH Grant Audit, 1956-1964 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Medical Center - Reorganization - Correspondence, Reports, Misc., 1960-1967 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Medical Center Computing, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 25)
- Medical Center Facts, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Medical Center Operations - Agreement Allocating Costs, #3, 1957-1961 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Medical Center Operations - City of Palo Alto Lease & Art. of Incorporation, 1955-1965 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Medical Center Operations - Core Facilities Agreement, #8, 1957-1967 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Medical Center Operations - Engineering Dept. Projects, 1962-1968 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Medical Center Operations - Financial Reports, 1958-1965 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Medical Center Operations - General, 1967-1972 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Medical Center Operations - General, 1, 1958-1965 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Medical Center Operations - General, 2, 1965-1967 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Medical Center Operations - Guarantees, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Medical Center Operations - Operating Agreement and By Laws, #4, 1956-1967 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Medical Center Operations - Reports by Stone & Rosenfield & Allen, 1955-1965 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Medical School - Grant Building Breezeway - Budget & Fiscal, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 19)
- Medical School - Grant Building Breezeway - Bulletins & Supplements, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 21)
- Medical School - Grant Building Breezeway - Contract Changes (empty folder) (Box 106, Folder 20)
- Medical School - Grant Building Breezeway - Disbursements, 1969-1973 (Box 106, Folder 18)
- Medical School - Grant Building Breezeway - Exhibits (empty folder) (Box 106, Folder 25)
- Medical School - Grant Building Breezeway - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 23)
- Medical School - Grant Building Breezeway - General Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 106, Folder 22)
- Medical School - Grant Building Breezeway - Legal, 1971-1973 (Box 106, Folder 17)
- Medical School - Grant Building Breezeway - Testing Laboratory Reports (empty folder) (Box 106, Folder 24)
- Medical School - Outdoor Primate Facility - Bulletins & Supplements, 571, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- Medical School - Outdoor Primate Facility - Contract Changes, 571, 1973-1974 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- Medical School - Outdoor Primate Facility - Exhibits, 571 (Box 113, Folder 9)
- Medical School - Outdoor Primate Facility - Fence, Affirmative Action Reports, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- Medical School - Outdoor Primate Facility - Field Insp. Progress Reports, 571, 1972-1974 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Medical School - Outdoor Primate Facility - Grading, Affirmative Action Reports, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 7)
- Medical School - Outdoor Primate Facility - Main Building, Affirmative Action Program, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- Medical School - Outdoor Primate Facility - Main Building, Affirmative Action Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- Medical School - Outdoor Primate Facility - Soil Investigation, 571, 1972-1973 (Box 113, Folder 10)
- Medical School - Outdoor Primate Facility - Testing Lab. Reports, 571, 1973-1974 (Box 113, Folder 8)
- Medical School Outdoor Primate Facility - Budget & Fiscal, #571, 1971-1974 (Box 112, Folder 27)
- Medical School Outdoor Primate Facility - Disbursements, #571, 1972-1975 (Box 112, Folder 25)
- Medical School Outdoor Primate Facility - General Correspondence, #571, 1969-1974 (Box 112, Folder 26)
- Medical School Outdoor Primate Facility - Legal II, #571, 1973-1974 (Box 112, Folder 23)
- Medical School Outdoor Primate Facility - Legal, #571, 1971-1973 (Box 112, Folder 24)
- Medical School Parking Lot - Legal Documents, 115A, 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Medical School Property Transactions (Title, etc.), 1906-1958 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Mello, Mrs. Anna C., 1949-1960 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Melvin, Roberts & Horwarth, 1942-1946 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Memorial Auditorium Improvements, 687, 1973-1975 (Box 109, Folder 25)
- Memorial Church, 1946-1972 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Memorial Hall - Auditorium, 1962-1970 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Memorial Hall - Custodian Duties, 1947-1957 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Memorial Hall, 1952-1962 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Menlo Park City School District, 1959 Expired (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Menlo Park, City of - Comprehensive Plan, 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Menlo Park, City of - General Plan, 1965-1973 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Menlo Park, City of - Master Plan, 1952 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Menlo Park, City of - Storm Drainage District, 1957-1963 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Menlo Park, City of, 1956-1973 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Mercantile Acceptance Corporation - Correspondence and Lease, 1955-1966 Terminated (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Merced Property (Geo. E. Crothers) - Mortgage, not real property - Doc. #505, 1943-1959 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Merchants Assoc. - Budget, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Merchants Assoc. - Financial Statements, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Merchants Assoc. - SU Contribution Status, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Merryman, John H., 1956-1959 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Metronics & Syntex - Power & Telephone Service, see: Hanover Ext. - Extra (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Metropolitan Transportation Comm., 1973 (Box 99, Folder 33)
- Meyer Library - Computer Cable to Main Library, 779, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 21)
- Meyer Library - Room 123 Alterations, 727, 1972-1973 (Box 105, Folder 12)
- Meyer, Charles J., 1962-1966 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Meyer, Henry J. (Estate), 1949-1955 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Mid-Peninsula Planning Study, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Midpeninsula Regional Park Dist., 1971-1976 (Box 99, Folder 32)
- Miles, Walter R. 1934-1946 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Miller, Robert E., 1962-1966 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Mineral Rights, 1960-1966 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Mineral Rights, 1960-1966 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Mirrielees, Edith R., 1936-1963 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous, 704, File IV, 1972-1973 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Mister "G" Sales Data, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Mitchum, Jones & Templeton, 1948-1962 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Mock, Arthur, 1960-1962 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Monrterey County - Est. of John E. Hamilton1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Moore House - Legal, 1963-1967 (Box 101, Folder 33)
- Morell, George, 1944-1963 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Morgan, Bayard Q., 1934-1968 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Morse, Frederick C. and Helen - dba Campus Bike Shop - Lease, 1968-1974 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Mortgage Loan Documents, estimated date range 1918-1952 (Box 74)
- Mortgage Loan Documents, estimated date range 1928-1954 (Box 75)
- Mortgage Loan Documents, Leases, misc., estimated date range 1887-1954 (Box 96)
- Moulton Report, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Myers, George S., 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Myhill, Marjorie Mrs., 1960-1965 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- NAACP Law Suit - Frenchman’s Terrace, 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 21)
- NACUBO (National Association of College and University Business Officers), 1973-1975 (Box 99, Folder 24)
- National Assoc. of College Univ. Bus. Officers, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- National Association of College and University Attorneys, Folder 2, 1967-1972 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- National Association of College and University Attorneys, Folder 3, 1973-1975 (Box 68, Folder 21)
- National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Neal, Phil C., 1955-1961 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- New Main Library, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 44)
- Newby, Hayes A., 1961-1967 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Newell, Henry Scholarship Fund, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 22)
- Newman, Joseph W., 1961-1965 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- News Clippings, Articles - Frenchman’s Terrace, 1972-1976 (Box 95, Folder 22)
- Notary Public - Kirk, Cassius L., Jr., 1960-1976 (Box 68, Folder 23)
- Nursery School - Legal Documents, 323, 1963-1966 (Box 103, Folder 15)
- Oakford, Robert V., 1962-1966 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Odell, Wm. R. & Mildred, 1948-1966 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Office of Development, 1969-1975 (Box 99, Folder 30)
- Old Chemistry Building Renovations - Legal, 1964-1965 (Box 103, Folder 12)
- Old Corporation Yard Conversion to Engineering - Legal, 499, 1966 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- Old Fire House Alterations, 699, 1972-1973 (Box 104, Folder 15)
- Old Pavilion Temporary Space - Bleacher Removal, #2, 705, 1973-1974 (Box 104, Folder 7)
- Old Pavilion Temporary Space, 705, 1972-1975 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- Old PBX Bldg. (Bldg. 2-250) IES Info. Center Alterations, (921), 1974-1975 (Box 108, Folder 22)
- Old Steam Plant - Alterations for Band, 1972-1975 (Box 109, Folder 29)
- Old Union 2nd Floor Alterations, 847, 1974-1975 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Old Union - Building 2-580 - Overseas Campus Alteration, 815, 1973-1975 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- Old Union - Financial Aids Alteration, 718, 1972-1973 (Box 105, Folder 10)
- Old Union - Financial Aids Building 2-580, Room 214 - Improvements, 834, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 36)
- Old Union 3rd Floor Alterations, 885, 1974-1975 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Old Union Basement Alteration, 846, 1973-1976 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Old Union, Rm 135 & 139 - Registrar Systems Analyst Office, 778, 1973-1975 (Box 103, Folder 21)
- O'Brien, Richard F., 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- O'Keefe, Daniel E., 1961-1966 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Open Space Plan, 1972-1974 (Box 99, Folder 34)
- Orange County - Bolsa Chica, 1959-1960 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Organizational Charts - “up through 1961” (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Organizational Charts, 1963-1966 (Binder) (Box 1)
- Ormondale Ranch - MacDonough Land, 1908-1935 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Otis, Brooks, 1958-1964 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Outdoor Primate Facility, 1969-1976 (Box 68, Folder 24)
- Outside Lease - Board of Trustees Parking #21, 600 California St., San Francisco (see Leasefile for 600 Calif.St.) (Box 68, Folder 26)
- Outside Lease - Med. Ctr. - Computer Services - 801 Welch Road, Terminated, 1973-1975 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- Outside Lease - Medicine (Heart Disease Prevention) - Gilroy, Watsonville, Expired, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 36)
- Outside Lease - Medicine, School of - Department of Pharmacology - 800 Welch Road, Expired, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- Outside Lease - Medicine, School of - Department of Psychiatry - 801 Welch Road, Suite 210, Expired, 1972-1975 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Outside Lease - Medicine, School of - Rm 204, 750 Welch Rd. - Immunology (Clinical Scholar Program), Expired, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- Outside Lease - Menlo Park - SRI - Bldg. 209, Stanford Village, Expired, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Outside Leases - Anthropology (East Asian Studies), 800 Welch Rd., Suite 240, 1970-1977 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Outside Leases - Chemistry - 265 San Antonio Way, Palo Alto (Zapata), Expired, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Outside Leases - Communications - Denver, Colorado, Terminated, 1972-1973 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Outside Leases - Education (SMSG), 2235 Old Middlefield Way, Mt. View, 1962-1976 (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Outside Leases - Education, School of (Cntr. for Research & Dev. in Teaching) - 1627 Bay Road, East Palo Alto, Ca., Expired, 1967-1971 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Outside Leases - Education, School of (Cntr. for Research & Dev. in Teaching) - 770 Welch Rd., Palo Alto, Ca., Terminated, 1965-1972 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Outside Leases - General, 1963-1976 (Box 68, Folder 25)
- Outside Leases - Hopkins Marine Station - Municipal Wharf #2, "Yellow Boat Concession," 1966-1973 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Outside Leases - Hopkins Marine Station, 301 Cannery Row, Monterey, CA, 1964-1970 TERMINATED (Box 67, Folder 17)
- Outside Leases - Medicine (Childhood Aphasia), 600 Willow Road, Palo Alto, 1969-1973 (Box 67, Folder 20)
- Outside Leases - Medicine (Pathology), 800 Welch Road, 1974-1977 (Box 67, Folder 19)
- Outside Leases - Medicine, 770 Welch Road, Suite 193, Assigned, 1974-1976 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Outside Leases - Medicine, School of - Suite 190, 770 Welch Road (Hare, Brewer & Kelley, Inc.), 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Outside Leases - Palo Alto - 1691 El Camino - Childhood Aphasia - Holiday Properties, #1605, Terminated, 1966-1970 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- Outside Leases - Palo Alto - 2095 East Bayshore Blvd. - Department of Psychology, Terminated, 1963-1966 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Outside Leases - Palo Alto - 2148 University (IMSSS), Expired, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Outside Leases - Palo Alto - 333 Hamilton Ave. - Dept. of Psychology (333 Investments), Terminated, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Outside Leases - Palo Alto - 407 Calif. Ave. - School of Education, Terminated, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Outside Leases - Palo Alto - 424 University - School of Education (Res. & Dev. Teaching Ctr), Terminated, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Outside Leases - Palo Alto - 701 Welch Rd. - Advisory Council on College Chemistry, 1965-1969 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Outside Leases - Palo Alto - 701 Welch Road., Suite 1119 - Genetics Dept., Terminated, 1965-1967 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Outside Leases - Palo Alto - 703 Welch Road, Suite C-4 - Dept. of Psychiatry, #1372, Expired, 1964-1966 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Outside Leases - Palo Alto - 770 Welch Rd. - Sublease from J. Brodie, School of Education, 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Outside Leases - Palo Alto - 800 Welch Rd., Suite 363 - School of Medicine, Terminated, 1963-1966 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Outside Leases - President’s Office, Assistant to (Black Student’s Volunteer Service) - 1898 Bay Rd., East Palo Alto, CA, Expired, 1971-1975 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Outside Leases - SEL - Leases for radioscience test sites in Arkansas (assigned to SRI), #1648, 1967-1971 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Outside Leases - SEL (for radioscience lab) - Kern Co., Ca. (Levan) (assigned to SRI), Expired, 1967-1973 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Outside Leases - SEL from Simon Newman Co., 211 ac. Merced County, (assigned to SRI), #1584, 1965-1970 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Outside Leases - SEL, 701 Welch Road, Suites 223, 225, 227, 229, 1975-1976 (Box 67, Folder 18)
- Outside Leases - SRI (Commissary, Stanford Village), Menlo Park, Ca., Expired, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Outside Leases - Stanford University Hospital - 800 Welch Road, PA, Ca., Expired, 1971-1975 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Outside Leases -City of Monterey waterfront lease (assigned by Hovden), Expired, 1967-1969 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Outside Properties - Almack, Mrs. J. C., San Mateo Co., Ca., #1, 1948-1969 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Outside Properties - Almack, Mrs. J. C., San Mateo Co., Ca., #2, 1970-1973 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Outside Properties - Almack, Mrs. J. C., San Mateo Co., Ca., Exhibits (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Outside Properties - Carlsmith, Donn W., Hawaii Co., Hawaii - Exhibits, SOLD (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Outside Properties - Carlsmith, Donn W., Hawaii Co., Hawaii, 1962-1975, SOLD (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Outside Properties - Carnochan, W. Bliss, San Mateo Co., CA, 1972-1976, SOLD (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Outside Properties - Cleophas, Gertrud, Ventura County, CA, 1973-1975, SOLD (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Outside Properties - Consolidated Foods Building, 2545 16th St., San Francisco, 1971-1973, SOLD (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Outside Properties - Consolidated Foods Corporation - Exhibits (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Outside Properties - Fisher, Anne, Payor: Anderson, Clarence, Notes Secured by Real Estate, 1972-1976 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Arrasmith, William, Los Angeles Co., 1973 (Box 66, Folder 28)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Bittson, Anthony, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Brace, Beverly O., Shingle Springs, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Bunkowski, Julius, Nevada, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Clock, Edwin H., 1975 (Box 66, Folder 24)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Devcoa Properties, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 25)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Dewolf Kellogg Charitable Trust, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 27)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Gertz, J. Barry, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 26)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Hagbom, Neldon (Palo Alto), 1972 (Box 66, Folder 29)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Hale, Mrs. C.P., Piedmont, CA, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Meyer, Olga (Elkhorn Slough, CA), 1974 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Orlando, Peter, (Santa Clara Co., CA), 1974 (Box 66, Folder 20)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Pittsburgh Plate Glass, 1968-1969 (Box 66, Folder 23)
- Outside Properties - Gifts Potential - Weaver & Palmer, Riverside County, 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Outside Properties - Harris, Dora, Los Angeles Co., #1 - Vansanta Way, Norton Ave., Sepulveda (Van Nuys), 1969-1973 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Outside Properties - Hawkins, Laura M., San Mateo County, CA, 1973-1977 SOLD (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Outside Properties - Kern County - Estate of Edith A. Stewart, SOLD, 1967-1970 (Box 64, Folder 21)
- Outside Properties - Kitteredge, Santa Clara Co., CA, 1972-1977 SOLD (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Outside Properties - Kolb, George, Los Angeles Co., CA, #1, 1967-1971 SOLD (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Outside Properties - Kolb, George, Los Angeles Co., CA, #2, 1972-1973 SOLD (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Outside Properties - Kolb, George, Los Angeles Co., CA, #3, 1973-1974 SOLD (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Outside Properties - Kolb, George, Los Angeles Co., CA, #4, 1974-1975 SOLD (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Outside Properties - Kolb, George, San Bernardino Co., CA, 1968-1975 SOLD (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Outside Properties - Lawson, Robert, Santa Cruz Co., CA (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Outside Properties - Leavell, C. H., El Paso Co., Texas, 1963-1972 SOLD (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Outside Properties - Lewis, Sumner G. L., Los Angeles Co., CA, 1968-1975 SOLD (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Outside Properties - Lingert, Alice A., San Bernardino Co., CA, 1961-1977 SOLD (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Outside Properties - Los Angelels Co. - Julian, W. R., SOLD, 1969-1971 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Outside Properties - Los Angeles - Lord, Wilma G., SOLD, 1968-1969 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Outside Properties - Los Angeles County - Boon Estate, Inglewood, SOLD, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Outside Properties - Los Angeles County - Brunner Property, Inglewood, SOLD, 1961-1967 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Outside Properties - Los Angeles County - Estate of Lawrence Newman, SOLD, 1953-1971 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Outside Properties - Mariposa County - Estate of Elmer Cox, SOLD, 1965-1967 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Outside Properties - McDonald, Isabelle, Sonoma Co., CA, #1, 1971-1972 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Outside Properties - McDonald, Isabelle, Sonoma Co., CA, #2, 1973 SOLD (Box 67, Folder 15)
- Outside Properties - McDonnell, Robert, Flathead Co., Montana, 1974-1976 SOLD (Box 67, Folder 16)
- Outside Properties - Mendocino County - Smith, Rosemary, SOLD, 1965-1971 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Outside Properties - Meredith, Mary C., San Luis Obispo Co., CA, SOLD, 1967-1976 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Outside Properties - Nickel, John C., Fresno Co., CA, SOLD, 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Outside Properties - Oregon - Multnomah County - Gift of Mr. Paul B. McKee, SOLD (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Outside Properties - Ralph J. Spiegl, Monterey Co. - Exhibits (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Outside Properties - Reversionary Interests, Santa Barbara County, SOLD, 1965-1968 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Outside Properties - San Bernardino County - Mr. & Mrs. Howe gift, Twenty-Nine Palms, SOLD, 1963-1967 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Outside Properties - San Francisco - Miscellaneous, University Owned, SOLD, 1941 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Outside Properties - San Mateo County - Estate of Ira S. Lillick, Atherton, SOLD, 1967-1968 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Outside Properties - San Mateo County - Estate of William W. Lyons, San Carlos, SOLD, 1966-1969 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Outside Properties - San Mateo County - Gift of Henry Chalfant, Jr., East Palo Alto, SOLD, 1967-1968 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Outside Properties - San Mateo County - Richard P. Ettinger Donative Sale, SOLD, 1966-1968 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Outside Properties - Santa Clara County - Eichler Property, Mountain View, SOLD, 1962-1968 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Outside Properties - Satterthwaite, A.P. & Todd, O.J., Skyline Boulevard, Santa Clara Co., CA, SOLD, 1972-1977 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Outside Properties - Sloan, W. H. (Salvation Army), Santa Clara Co., CA, 1951-1960 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Outside Properties - Swayne, Lloyd, Sr., Solano Co., CA, SOLD, 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Outside Properties - Takahashi, Henri H., San Francisco City and Co., CA, SOLD, 1974-1976 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Outside Properties - Tawney, Charles, Payor: Menghetti, Peter, Notes secured by Real Estate, 1963-1966 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Outside Properties - Tolman, Mrs. C. F., Santa Clara Co., CA, SOLD, 1964-1974 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Outside Properties - Walbridge, Lenore K., Ventura Co., CA, SOLD, 1963-1975 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Outside Properties - Weston, Austin - Notes Secured by Real Estate, DEAD, 1967-1968 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Outside Properties # - Gomes Alfred, Santa Clara Co., CA 1969-1973 (Box 69, Folder 19)
- Outside Properties #1 - Bonn, Norman (AKA Bonacich), Santa Clara & San Mateo Cos., CA, 1974-1976, SOLD (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Outside Properties #1 - Bonsall, Mabel, Monterey County, CA, 1966-1976, SOLD (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Outside Properties #1 - Boyd, Walter, Los Angeles Co., CA, Notes Secured by Real Estate, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Outside Properties #1 - Cordes, William F., San Francisco City & County, CA, 1974-1976, SOLD (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Outside Properties #1 - Gifts Potential - La Riviere, F. David, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Outside Properties #2 - Gomes Alfred, Santa Clara Co., CA 1973-1975 (Box 69, Folder 18)
- Outside Properties, Bailey, Bertha C., Santa Clara Co., CA, SOLD (Box 68, Folder 27)
- PACE - Campaign Plant Components, 1961-1964 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Pacific Electrical & Mechanical Co., 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Pacific Gas & Electric Co. - Documents, 1956-1960 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Pacific Gas & Electric Co. - New Easements - Mt. View, Potrero Gas Line, 1947-1949 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Pacific Gas & Electric Co. - Right of Use Permit - Gas Main, 1949-1957 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Pacific Gas & Electric Co., 1963-1970 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Pacific Gas and Electric Co., 9/1/1958-8/30/1963 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Pacific Grove Property, 1938-1942 (Box 41, Folder 16)